♪ If I ♪
♪ Should stay ♪
♪ I would only be in ♪
♪ Your way ♪
♪ So I'll go ♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ I'll think of you ♪
♪ Every step of ♪
♪ The way ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ Ooh I ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ My darling you ♪
♪ Mm mm ♪
♪ Bittersweet ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ That is all I'm taking ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ So goodbye ♪
♪ Please don't cry ♪
♪ We both know ♪
♪ I'm not what you ♪
♪ You need ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ Ooh I ♪
♪ You ooh ♪
(saxophone playing)
♪ I hope ♪
♪ Life treats you kind ♪
♪ And I hope ♪
♪ You have all you ♪
♪ Dreamed of ♪
♪ And I wish you joy ♪
♪ And happiness ♪
♪ But above all this ♪
♪ I wish you love ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ Ooh I ♪
♪ I will always ♪
♪ Love you ♪
♪ Ooh I ♪
♪ Will always ♪
♪ Love you ♪
♪ Ooh I ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ I will always ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Darling I love you ♪
♪ Oh I'll always ♪
♪ I'll always ♪
♪ Love you ♪